<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Because Personal Sites are the New Black on</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in Because Personal Sites are the New Black on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 09:41:42 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 09:41:42 +1000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>I am an experienced developer who practices development for a profession and a hobby. I regularly contribute to open source projects, and am one of the maintainers of the Authelia open source project.
My day job is relatively broad but mostly revolves around data analysis; but also has a healthy level of devops type workloads, systems integration, and general automation.
Kubernetes I love Kubernetes. I run a fairly nice highly available home cluster specifically for experimenting and general hobbying.</description></item><item><title>Blog</title><link>/blog/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 09:41:42 +1000</pubDate><guid>/blog/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Docs</title><link>/docs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 09:41:42 +1000</pubDate><guid>/docs/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 19:23:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>/privacy-policy/</guid><description>TLDR: We do not use cookies and we do not collect any personal data.
Website visitors No personal information is collected. No information is stored in the browser. No information is shared with, sent to or sold to third-parties. No information is shared with advertising companies. No information is mined and harvested for personal and behavioral trends. No information is monetized. Information we collect and what we use it for We run Plausible analytics on getdoks.</description></item></channel></rss>